Guide to the Janet G. Travell papers, 1910-1997 MS0704.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Conferences, symposiums, and lectures, 1946-1995; MS0704 Series 1; 8 Linear feet (Box 11, Box 12, Box 13, Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 10, Box 16, Box 17, Box 4, Box 3, Box 6, Box 5, Box 14, Box 15, Box 2, Box 1)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Fourth Conference on Cold Injury, Princeton, NJ, 11/07/1955 -11/09/1955 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Franklin General Hospital conference on Neurogenic and Myofascial Pain, Valley Stream, NY, 11/04/1986 -11/06/1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Franklin General Hospital conference on Neurogenic and Myofascial Pain, Valley Stream, NY, 11/04/1986 -11/06/1986 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Franklin Hospital Medical Center conference on Neuropathic and Musculoskeletal Pain, 04/16/1991 -04/19/1991 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Funt, Lawrence and Cranio-Fascial Pain Center, Bethesda, MD, 05/1993 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Conferences, Lectures: George Washington University, Division of Rehabilitation rounds - Chest Wall Pain, 04/08/1971 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Georgetown Hospital Lecture, 10/29/1963 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Georgetown University School of Dentistry, (non-lecture), 02/17/1978 -02/18/1978 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Glenndale Hospital lecture, 05/11/1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Gnathological Study Group, Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 02/02/1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Goldwater Memorial Hospital lecture on Chest Pain, 05/20/1958 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Greater Long Island dental meeting, Uniondale, NY, 04/05/1978 -04/07/1978 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Greater New York Dental Meeting, 12/07/1960 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Guadalajara Architecture workshop, 02/13/1975 -02/14/1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Guadalajara Seat Design Lectures, 02/1975 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Conferences, Lectures: GW Hospital Lecture on "Torticollis", 01/17/1961 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Heat and Cold Therapy Conference, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Home Fashions League, Inc. lecture on seating design, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Honolulu, 02/21/1960 -02/27/1960 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Hotel Gotham lecture on Head, Face, and Jaw Pain, 05/12/1958 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Houston District Dental Society lecture, 11/15/1978 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Houston VA Hospital lecture, 02/06/1969 -02/07/1969 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Indiana University School of Medicine conference, 10/06/1966 -10/07/1966 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Conferences, Lectures: International Association for the Study of Pain, Florence, Italy, 09/05/1975 -09/08/1975 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Conferences, Lectures: International Association for the Study of Pain (IASP), NY, NY, 10/21/1977 -10/22/1977 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Conferences, Lectures: International Association for the Study of Pain, Montreal, 08/27/1978-09/01/1978 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Conferences, Lectures: International College of Cranial-Mandibular Orthopaedics meeting, 09/22/1982 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Conferences, Lectures: International Federation Manual Medicine conference, Prague, 10/09/1974 -10/12/1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Conferences, Lectures: International Physiological Congress, Montreal, 08/31/1953 -09/04/1953 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Interstate Postgraduate Medical Association of North America conference, Washington, DC, 10/19/1966 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Interstate Postgraduate Medical Association conference, Washington, DC, 10/17/1966 -10/20/1966 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Janet Travell Seminar on Myofascial Pain, San Francisco, 01/15/1982 -01/16/1982 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Janet Travell Soft Tissue Pain Management Award, American Academy of Pain Management conference, Knoxville, TN, 10/14/1993 -10/17/1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Johns Hopkins Rehabilitative Medicine lecture, 02/25/1993 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation Conference - Pain Mechanisms In Tissues, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation Conference on Cold Injury, NY, NY, 11/20/1952 -11/21/1952 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation Conference, NY, NY, 02/14/1952 -02/16/1952 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation Conference on Cold Injury, Fort Churchill, Canada, 02/21/1954 -02/25/1954 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation Connective Tissue Conferences, 1950 -1952 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation Connective Tissues Conference, Princeton, NJ, 02/18/1953 -02/20/1953 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation Fifth Conference on Cold Injury, Ladd A.F.B, Alaska, 03/10/1957 -03/15/1957 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Journal Club of Buffalo lecture, 05/23/1963 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Kessler Institute for Rehabilitation, Inc. meeting, 04/11/1992 -04/12/1992 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Lawrence Funt course for Australian M.D.'s, Bethesda, MD, 05/03/1986 -05/09/1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Lecture at Long Beach V.A. Hospital, 04/1974 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Lecture at the Manor Club, Pelham, NY, 03/14/1972 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Lecture Notes from Memphis lecture, 09/22/1982 -09/23/1982 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Lecture Notes from San Francisco lecture, 01/14/1983 -01/15/1983 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Lecture on "External Support in Seated Posture,"(University of Iowa), 11/09/1963 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Lecture on "Muscular Sources of Back Pain," before the American College of Surgeons, Baltimore, 04/25/1961 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Lecture on Myofascial Pain (NIH), 09/24/1962 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Lecture Schedule Prior to, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Lecture Schedule, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Lecture to Sir Walter Cabinet, Raleigh, NC, 05/18/1965 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Lecture to wives of George Washington University Medical Students, 11/13/1968 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Lecture Trips, 1976-1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Lectures, 1955-1960 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Lectures, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Long Beach State College lecture, 12/08/1975 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Los Angeles College of Chiropractic seminar, 11/12/1988 -11/13/1988 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Loyola University School of Dentistry lecture, 10/12/1973 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Magazine Publishers Association, Inc. conference, Washington, DC, 03/24/1963 -03/27/1963 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Maimonides Dental Society meeting, Silver Spring, MD, 01/27/1981 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Maryland Academy of Family Physicians, Annapolis, MD, 11/29/1980 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Mecklenburg County Medical Society meeting, Charlotte, NC, 10/03/1950 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Medical College of Georgia (Augusta) Myofascial Pain lecture, 05/13/1994 -05/14/1994 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Medical College of Georgia, School of Dentistry conference, Augusta, Georgia, 09/20/1985 -09/21/1985 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Medical Society for the County of N.Y., 1961-1974 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Medical Society of the State of New York Exhibit on Trigger Points, 05/17/1948 -05/21/1948 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Medical Society of the State of New York - Referred Pain From Skeletal Muscle, NY, NY, 05/10/1954 -05/14/1954 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Meeting with Lawrence Funt, Washington, DC, 07/14/1982 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Memphis Dental Society, Wednesday, 09/23/1982 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Menninger Foundation lecture on Chest and Arm Pain, Topeka, KS, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Metropolitan New York Society of Oral Surgeons, 11/16/1959 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Michigan Cranial Fascial Cervical Pain Dysfunction meeting, Detroit, 06/17/1983 -06/18/1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Middlesex General Hospital seminar, 03/24/1982 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Minnesota Academy For Gnathological Research, 09/1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Movie for American Academy General Practice, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Muscular Dystrophy Association of America, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Musculoskeletal Pain Associated with Craniofacial Syndromes meeting, Pittsburgh, PA, 03/03/1989 -03/04/1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Myofascial Pain And Dysfunction seminar, Newport Beach, CA, 04/16/1983 -04/18/1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Myofascial Pain lecture, Sharon, Connecticut, 08/19/1950 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Myofascial Pain lecture, Long Beach V.A. Hospital, Dec., 1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Myofascial Pain seminar, Wichita, Kansas, 05/11/1984 -05/12/1984 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Myofascial Pain seminars, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Myofascial Pain Symposium at Walter Reed Army Medical Center, 11/1983 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Myofascial Pain Symposium, Newport Beach, Calif., 04/07/1984 -04/09/1984 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Myofascial Pain workshop, Atlanta, Ga., 04/26/1986 -04/27/1986 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Myofascial T.P. Pain Institute, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Myofascial Trigger Point Workshop, Bethseda, MD, 01/13/1995 -01/15/1995 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Myotronics Inc. Conference, Orlando, FL, 03/04/1988 -03/06/1988 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Conferences, Lectures: North American Academy of Manipulative Medicine (NAAMM), 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Conferences, Lectures: North American Academy Manipulative Medicine (NAAMM) conference, San Francisco, CA, Aug., 1966 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Conferences, Lectures: North American Academy of Manipulative Medicine (NAAMM) conference, New York, NY, 03/19/1967 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Conferences, Lectures: North American Academy of Manipulative Medicine (NAAMM) conference, Miami Beach, FL, 08/19/1967 -08/21/1967 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM conference lecture "Muscle Dysfunction in Manual Medicine," Montreal, 08/29/1968 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM, 1969-1971 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM conference, Chicago, 04/26/1969 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM conference, UCLA, 11/08/1969 -11/09/1969 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM conference - University of Southern Calif., 11/09/1969 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM conference - Liaison Committee, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM conference - Business, Los Angeles, 11/08/1969 -11/09/1969 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM conference, Banff, Canada, 09/09/1970 -09/12/1970 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM conference, Miami Beach, FL, 10/20/1972 -10/24/1972 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM Council meeting, 03/04/1972 -03/05/1972 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM, Phoenix, Arizona, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM conference, Toronto, 10/21/1976 -10/23/1976 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM conference, Williamsburg, VA, 11/17/1977 -11/20/1977 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM conference, Los Angeles, 10/25/1978 -10/29/1978 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM conference, Las Vegas, NV, 10/28/1987 -10/31/1987 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM meeting, 10/15/1980 -10/18/1980 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Conferences, Lectures: North American Academy of Manipulative Medicine (NAAMM) meeting lecture on Quadratus Lumborum Muscle and Vapocoolant Spray, Sanibel, FL, 10/15/1980 -10/18/1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM meeting, San Antonio, TX, 11/11/1981 -11/14/1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM meeting, Ontario, Canada, 09/28/1982 -10/01/1982 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM meeting, 10/19/1983 -10/22/1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM meeting San Diego, CA, November, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM meeting, Boston, 10/15/1986 -10/19/1986 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM meeting, Las Vegas, NV, 10/28/1987 -10/31/1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NAAMM meeting, Clearwater, Fla., 10/19/1989 -10/21/1989 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Conferences, Lectures: National Education Association symposium, Washington, DC, 05/08/1968 -05/10/1968 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New Haven Dental lecture, 03/03/1960 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Academy of Medicine - Cardiac Pain exhibit, 10/08/1951 -10/19/1951 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Academy of Medicine Clinical Research Meeting, 03/02/1950 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Academy of Medicine conference, 06/06/1977 -06/10/1977 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Academy of Medicine lecture on Ergonovine, 05/25/1956 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Academy of Medicine Scientific Exhibit - Musculo-Skeletal System, Oct.9-20, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Academy of Medicine/Virchow Society symposium, 12/02/1957 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Academy of Science conference, 03/24/1960 -03/26/1960 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Academy of Sciences conference, Princeton, NJ, 10/1964 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Academy of Sciences symposium - Stimulant laxatives, 05/09/1953 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Chiropractic College seminar on Low Back Pain, Baltimore, MD, 04/20/1991 -04/21/1991 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Chiropractic College symposium, East Rutherford, NJ, 09/13/1990 -09/16/1990 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Chiropractic College symposium, Old Brookville, NY, 10/20/1990 -10/21/1990 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Rheumatism Association, 1957-1960 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Rheumatism Association Clinical Conference on seating design, 01/1952 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Rheumatism Association Conference, 03/15/1950 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Rip Van Winkle Clinic, Hudson, NY, 01/1951 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Society of Physical Medicine - Somatic Pain Syndrome, 12/02/1953 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York State Exhibit, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York State Medical Society conference, 02/18/1957 -02/21/1957 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Conferences, Lectures: New York Wellesley Club lecture, 01/12/1955 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Newport Harbor Academy of Dentistry meeting, 05/18/1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Conferences, Lectures: NIH Dental Research lecture, 12/06/1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Niehans, Paul-"Fountain of Youth" therapy, 1959 -1960 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Conferences, Lectures: North American Academy of Musculoskeletal Medicine (NAAMM) conference, Clearwater Beach, FL, 10/19/1989 -10/21/1989 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Northern Virginia Consortium for Continuing Medical Education, 06/06/1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Notes for Chicago Pain Symposium, 04/1953 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Ondontorgraphic Society of Chicago lecture, 04/06/1969 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Original drawings for lantern slides: Hypometabolic Syndrome presentation, New York state, 02/18/1957 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Orthodontic Studies Society lecture, Washington, DC, 01/29/1977 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Orthopaedic Audio-Synopsis Foundation tape recording, Los Angeles, 11/1969 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Otis Air Force Base (MA) lecture on sitting comfortably, 05/09/1964 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Pain and Muscle Spasm lecture, Doctors Hospital (DC), 12/06/1974 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Pain Conference, George Washington University, 05/17/1984 -05/19/1984 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Pain lecture, Long Beach V.A. Hospital, 10/24/1974 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Pain Rehabilitation Center, Mesa, Arizona, 04/1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Palm Springs Seminars, Inc. lectures, 1984 -1986 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Palm Springs Seminars, Inc. lectures, 01/17/1987 -01/18/1987 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Palm Springs Seminars, Inc. lectures, 11/21/1987 -11/22/1987 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Palm Springs Seminars, Inc. lectures, 04/09/1988 -04/10/1988 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Palm Springs Seminars, Inc. lectures, 11/10/1990 -11/11/1990 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Palo Duro Dental Study Group, Amarillo, TX, 10/07/1977 -10/08/1977 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Parenteral Drug Association meeting, NY, NY, 10/20/1954 -10/22/1954 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Permanente Clinic, 11/14/1969 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Pharmacology of Procaine lecture, 02/01/1955 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Philadelphia Conferences, 1965 -1966 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Philadelphia lecture on Management of Painful Muscle Spasm, 11/26/1958 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Phoenix (Ariz.) Academy of Dentistry, 01/27/1984 -01/28/1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Physical Fitness - Aerobics, Dallas, TX, 03/13/1973 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Physical Therapy symposium - Dr. Lawrence Funt, Chevy Chase, MD, 02/27/1985 -03/02/1985 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Pierce County Dental Society lecture, Tacoma, WA, 02/02/1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Practitioners Conference lecture, NY, NY, 10/27/1954 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Practitioner's Conference- Sciatica & Low Back Pain, 05/09/1951 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Prospective documentary on the career of Janet Travell, Boston meeting, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Providence Hospital lecture, Southfield, MI, 04/26/1985 -04/27/1985 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Providence Hospital lecture, Southfield, MI, 04/26/1985 -04/27/1985 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Quadratus Lumborum muscle lectures, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Rehabilitation Education, Inc. course, Bloomfield, NJ, 09/24/1994 -09/25/1994 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Rehabilitation Education, Inc. course, Newport Beach, CA, 05/20/1995 -05/21/1995 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Rehabilitation Education Inc. meeting, 03/09/1991 -03/10/1991 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Rehabilitation Education Inc. meeting, 09/28/1991 -09/29/1991 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Rehabilitation Education, Inc. seminar, Cherry Hill, NJ, 10/21/1995 -10/22/1995 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Rheumatism seminar, Washington, DC, 06/09/1982 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Rheumatology Research Meeting, Minneapolis, MN, 05/06/1989 -05/07/1989 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Rice University, Architects and seating design, 09/24/1972 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Robert B. Brigham Hospital lecture, Boston, 04/04/1979 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Rowe Smith Memorial Foundation seminar, Bandera, TX, 03/16/1978 -03/19/1978 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Russell W. Bunting Periodical Study Club meeting, Lansing, MI, 10/05/1989 -10/06/1989 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Conferences, Lectures: San Fernando Dental Society lecture, 03/19/1980 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Conferences, Lectures: School of Dentistry, University of Maryland (Baltimore) seminar, 07/12/1978 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Seaboard Medical Association meeting, Nags Head, NC, 06/16/1967 -06/18/1967 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Second International Congress of Physical Medicine, Copenhagen, Denmark, 08/20/1956 -08/24/1956 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Seminar "Trapezius muscle pain and its treatment", 11/29/1983 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Seminar at home of Robert Gerwin, 11/06/1985 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Seton Hall College of Medicine symposium, Jersey City, NJ, 01/27/1960 -02/03/1960 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Seventh Annual Pain Symposium - Walter Reed, 09/16/1983 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Shoulder Symposium, GWU, 04/19/1980 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Society of Oral Physiology and Occlusion meeting, NY, NY, 12/05/1959 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Society of Oral Physiology and Occlusion meeting, NY, NY, 12/05/1971 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Society of Oral Physiology and Occlusion meeting (non-lecture), 11/27/1977 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Conferences, Lectures: South Shore County Medical Society lecture, 01/18/1956 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Special Education Conference, Washington, DC, 04/03/1969 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Conferences, Lectures: St. Peter's General Hospital lecture, New Brunswick, NJ, 02/28/1951 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Syllabus - Firts International West Coast Symposium on Myofascial Trigger Point Pain, San Diego, CA, 03/02/1995 -03/05/1995 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Symposium on Musculoskeletal Pain, Fairfax Hospital (VA), 04/24/1976 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Symposium on Myofascial Pain - Minneapolis, MN, 05/08/1989 -05/10/1989 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Temple University Episcopal Hospital, Philadelphia, 03/26/1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Temporomandibular Joint and Orofacial Pain Center, St. Louis, MO, 05/1983 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Conferences, Lectures: Tennessee Cranio Winter Meeting, Nashville, 01/14/1988 -01/20/1988 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Conferences, Lectures: The American Academy of Pain Management conference, Stockton, CA, 09/14/1990 -09/16/1990 (Box 14, Folder 16)